All right, Katou-san.
（英梨々）じゃあ　加藤さん。
今度は　ムッとした表情で　お願い。
Give me a huffy expression this time, please.
H-Huffy?
（恵）ム…　ムッとした？
Um, it's like...
えっと…　ほら
彼氏に　デート　すっぽかされて→
Imagine you're stood up
by your boyfriend, so you go:
「何よ　何よ！
あんたなんか　もう知らない！」→
"What the hell? You're dead to me now!"
みたいな感じ。
It's something like that.
You'd never actually have to behave or talk like that in real life, though.
そういう態度や　言葉遣い
現実で使うシチュエーション　ないよ。
（倫也）《とうとう　俺たちの
サークル活動が　始まった》
Our circle activities have begun at last.
（倫也）詩羽先輩も　どうぞ。
I got you some too, Utaha-senpai.
Ahhh~
Utaha-senpai?
詩羽先輩？
Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~
Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~
Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~
Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~
Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~
Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~
Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~
Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~ Ahhh~
Another
Another Another Another Another Another Another Another Another Another
Another Another
Another Another Another
Another Another Another Another
Another Another Another Another Another
Another Another Another Another Another Another
≪（鉛筆の折れる音）
≪（恵）キャッ！
いけない　鉛筆が折れちゃった…。
No good. My pencil broke.
Go buy me another one immediately, Tomoya.
今すぐ　買ってきて　倫也。
houkago futari de sugoshita kyoushitsu
Whenever we're together in the classroom after school
tsukue no ue muchuu de hazumu kimi no koe
You at your desk, just talking and talking on and on
donkan na kimi no sono taido ga
You're so dense, and it really shows
itsumo watashi wo ijiwaru ni saseru no
And that's why I always have to pick on you
hitoribocchi da to omou toki mo aru
Sometimes I feel like I'm alone
namida tomerarenai hi mo aru
Some days I can't stop myself from crying
hontou no watashi wo mitsumete hoshii no
I want you to look and see the real me
kitto tsutawaru to shinjiteiru yo
I'll keep believing that one day you will
kimi wa itsudatte itsudatte kawaranai kara
But you just never, ever, never, ever change, and so
watashi ga nankai mo nankai mo signal okutteageru
I keep sending and sending and sending and sending the same signal
yume mita ano oka mezashite
Dreaming of the day I'll make it over that hill
kujikesou na toki mo ganbaresou da yo
Even when I feel like giving up, I can keep going on
kimi ga iru kara
Because you're there for me
The Date Event of Mismatching Viewpoints
（英梨々）何それ…　加藤さん
あなた　ジト目もできないの？
What do you mean?
Katou-san, can't you even do a disgusted glare?
じゃあ　次は
怒ったときの表情　やってみて。
Then, try just giving me an angry expression next.
Do it like there's an anger mark on your temple.
こめかみに
怒りマーク　入れる感じで。
You can't do that either?
それも　駄目…。
じゃあ　汗マークは？
How about a sweat drop, then?
Don't tell me you can't even get
those vertical lines on your face?
（英梨々）もしかして
顔に　縦線も入らないの？
これじゃあ　表情パターンが
何一つ　作れないじゃない！→
How am I supposed to design
any standard expressions like this?!
Just what am I supposed to do now?!
いったい　どうすればいいのよ！
I'm not sure how I can respond to that.
どうしろと言われても…。
I'll go and try doing some self-study.
ちょっと　自主練してくる。
「何よ　何よ　あんたなんか
もう知らない」→
What the hell? You're dead to me now.
「あっ　あんたのために
やったんじゃないから→
Oh, I'm not doing any of this for you,
so don't get the wrong idea.
誤解しないでよね」
（英梨々）あ～…。
苦戦してるみたいだな。
Looks like you're having a rough time.
こんな大変なミッション
今までに　経験したことないわ。
Never in my life have I
taken on a mission this rough.
そっか。
I see.
Maybe if she were deadpan and emotionless,
これが　無表情の無感情なら→
then we'd be able to play her off
as a character similar to Ayanami Rei.
綾波系キャラとして
確立できるけど→
彼女の場合　中途半端に
キャラが薄いのよね。
But it's more like her personality's
neither here nor there.
Ah, I know what you mean.
あ～　そうだよな。
It's not so much that she has no emotions.
別に　感情が
ないわけじゃないからな。
感情表現が適当なだけで。
It's just that she doesn't
put her heart into expressing them.
Seriously, I've never worked
with a useless character before.
ホント　ここまで使えないキャラ
初めて。
See? She's got no character at all!
なっ？　マジ　キャラ立ってないだろ？俺が言ったとおりだろ？
Didn't I say so?
Hearing you boast about something so pointless is so annoying.
そういう無意味な自慢されると
イラッとくる…。
At any rate, there's not a lot of time left before our character design deadline.
それはともかく
キャラデザの締め切りも→
そんなに　余裕ないぞ？
You're not wrong there.
そうなのよね～。
今週末　倫也の家に集まって
一気に仕上げちゃおっかな。
Maybe we should meet at your place
this weekend and just knock it all out at once.
えっ…　今週末？
Wait, this weekend?
What about it? Do you have something planned?
何？　用でもあんの？
いや…。
Well...
On another note, Eriri...
ところでさ　英梨々。
（英梨々）何？
What?
Have you ever been on a date?
デートって　したことあるか？
え？　え？
（英梨々）ああああ～！！
Is it really that shocking a question?
いや　俺　そんなに
すごい質問　したか？
Just hearing the word come out of the mouth of a gross otaku like you is cringeworthy!
（英梨々）あんたみたいな
キモオタの口から→
そんな単語が出たら
誰でも　鳥肌　立つわよ！→
デデデ…　デートだなんて…。→
A-A date... D-D—
誘ってる？
ない。
Are you asking me out?
No.
（英梨々）アウェーでの戦い方？
So you want an away game strategy?
Look, it's really just hypothetical.
だから　これは
本当に　例えばの話なんだけどさ→
ショッピングモールで
女の子と　服　見たりとか→
Let's say a girl ropes you in to going to
the mall to look at clothes and stuff with her.
そういう状況に
追い込まれたとするじゃん。
行かないわよ　あたし。
I wouldn't go to a place
flooded with human mobs.
そんな　人が　ごみのような所。
人混みと言え。
Just call it crowded.
だいたい　服だったら→
If you need to get clothes,
通販か　コーディネーターさんに
見立ててもらえばいいじゃない。
why not just mail order them or
have a coordinator pick them out for you?
Try to put aside your special
Milady Shut-In quirks for a minute.
引きこもりお嬢さまの特殊性は
置いといてだな。
What I'm trying to ask is, if you were caught in
a suffocating situation like that, what would you do?
つまり　そういう
息苦しい状況になったとき→
お前なら　どうする？
何で　それを　あたしに聞くの？
Why are you asking me?
お前なら
分かってるんじゃないかと思ってな。
I figured that you'd probably know what to do.
学校じゃ　いつも
仮面　かぶってる　お前なら。
After all, you always wear a mask at school.
あっ…　いや　悪い！
変なこと言った。　忘れてくれ。
Oh, sorry! That was a weird thing to say.
Forget I said it.
ハァ…。
そうね
アウェーでの戦い方なら…。
Well, if we're talking away game strategy,
引き分け狙いね。
引き分け？
just aim for a draw.
A draw?
Do a bit of research prior to the event and
stay on her conversational level as much as possible.
ある程度　下調べして
できる限り　話を合わせて→
それでも　つらくなったら…。
If it still gets too hard...
笑顔で　ごまかす。
笑顔？
just put up a smile and fake it.
A smile?
Yep. Even if you have no idea
what the other person's talking about,
そう。　向こうが　何言っているのか分からなくても→
just smile and nod.
取りあえず　笑顔。
余計な質問は自重。
周囲から浮くような言動はしない。
Restrain yourself from
asking anything unnecessary.
Don't do anything that makes you stick out like a sore thumb.
こっちの主張を　ごり押しなんて
もっての外。
And definitely don't do anything dumb
like trample her opinions with your own.
Don't you think that's kind of boring?
何か　それって
つまんなくないか？
せっかく　一緒にいるんなら→
If we'd gone to the trouble of finding time to
spend together, shouldn't it be a bit deeper than that?
もっと　濃い時間を
過ごしたいと思うだろ？
だから　そういうのは　ホーム。
Well that would be the home game strategy.
That works if you're playing on the otaku field.
オタクのフィールドで
やればいいのよ。
But I've always wanted to
just be my usual self all the time.
でも　俺は
いつでも　いつもの自分でいたい。
（英梨々）そんなのは　無理よ。
誰だって　裏の顔を持ってる。
That's impossible.
Everyone's got a secret side to them.
But... Katou doesn't, does she?
けど　加藤は　そうじゃないだろ？
She's not an otaku, but even when she mingles
with us, she's the same way she always is, right?
あいつ　非オタなのに
俺たち　オタクに交じっても→
全然　いつもどおりだろ？
I think that's actually a pretty
amazing thing about her.
俺　あいつの　そういうところは
ある意味　すごいなって。
So I mean, I don't think I should just
settle for a draw and force a smile with her.
だから　何て言うか　あいつ相手に
引き分け狙いとか　愛想笑いとか→
そういうのは
したくないなって…。
So this was about a real date, after all.
（英梨々）やっぱり
リアルデートなんじゃない。→
相手　加藤さんなんじゃない。
えっ？
You're going out with Katou-san, aren't you?
Huh?
So I was nothing but a trial run
after all the times you've relied on me?
散々　頼っておいて
結局は　当て馬とか→
この澤村　英梨々も
なめられたものよね！
How dare you treat me, Sawamura Eriri, like this!
It's not like that!
いや　違う　単なる買い物だ。
We're just going shopping!
六天馬モールのオープニングセールに
付き合うだけなんだよ。
I'm going with her to
the Rokutenba Mall opening sale!
だから　それを
デートって言うんじゃない！
That's exactly what you call a date!
I knew that was a date.
やっぱ　デートだよな…。
Even if it were with a cousin, that's still a date!
いとこ相手でも
デートになっちゃうよな！
何の話よ　それ…　って。
≪（詩羽）フフフ…　フフ…。
What are you even talking about?
（詩羽）フフ…。
う…　詩羽…　先輩？
U-Utaha-senpai?
（詩羽）きた！
プロット　浮かんできた！
I've got it! The plot's come to me at last!
The protagonist casts aside the
yandere heroine to date another girl.
ヤンデレヒロインを差し置いて→
他の女と　デートに行ってしまった主人公。→
But when he returns home, he's knocked unconscious by a sudden blow to the back of the head.
自宅に帰ってきてみると
いきなり後頭部を殴られ気絶。→
He wakes to find his arms and legs bound. Unable to move, he calls for help when who should appear before him but...
気が付いたら　手足を拘束されて
身動きもとれず→
助けを呼んだところに
現れたのは　何と！
なあ…　あれって…。
Hey, what's with her?
創作しているときには
時々あることよ。
That comes out every now and then during the creative process.
クリエーターの闇ね。
The darkness in the creator's heart.
ただ　ノッてるだけなんだよな！？
そうなんだよな！？
She's just in the zone, right? Right?!
お仕置きが必要ですね　倫理君。
Looks like you need to be punished, Mr. Ethical.
Hang on a second! She just called him Mr. Ethical!
ちょっと待って！
今　倫理君って言った！
Um...
（恵）えっと…。→
Wh-Why should I be so worried
about a guy like him?
「なっ　何で　私が
あんなやつのことなんか→
気にしなくちゃいけないのよ」→
Dating Sim Proposal
So...
（詩羽）というわけで→
I stayed up all last night and came up with a plot.
ゆうべ　徹夜して
プロット　上げてきたから。
早っ！
うわ～　分厚い。
So fast!
Wow, it's so thick.
You wrote all of this in one day?
これ　たった一日で　書いたんだ。
This looks about five times bigger
than the proposal Tomoya wrote.
（英梨々）倫也が書いた企画書の
５倍くらい　分量がありそうね。
何だか　ものすごーく→
I can't pretend that I'm not humbled by this,
耳が痛い気が
しないでもないけど…。
さすが　詩羽先輩だぜ！
but that's Utaha-senpai for you!
まずは　一通り読んでみて
意見を聞かせてちょうだい。
Just read it over for now
so you can tell me what you think.
私　しばらく寝てるから。
I'm gonna sleep for a bit.
早っ！
So fast.
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
「親の転勤により→
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
When he's forced to move to a
suburban town by his parents' work,
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
とある地方都市に　引っ越してきた
主人公　安曇　誠司は→
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
For Mr. Ethical, By Mr. Ethical
Overflowing with Ethics
Super Clean Dating Sim Plan (Tentative)
the protagonist, Azumi Seiji,
on his first visit to his new school,
転校初日に　桜　舞い散る　坂の上で一人の少女と出会う」
has a fateful encounter with a girl atop a hill amongst falling cherry blossom petals.
（恵）えっと　この主人公も
澤村さんのデザイン？
Um... Is this your design of the
protagonist that's showing, Sawamura-san?
（英梨々）まあ…　あたしの考えた
最強のイケメンってことで。
Well, he's the most handsome guy I could think up.
「翌日　転校先のクラスで
偶然の再会を果たす」
The next day, when he's introduced to his
new class, they share another chance encounter.
Ugh. That's such a clichéd development.
（英梨々）うわ…　ベタな展開。
The girl's name is Kanou Meguri.
「少女の名は　叶　巡璃といった」
（恵）
うわ…　何か　どっかで聞いた名前。
I feel like I've heard that name before.
Bit by bit, Seiji and Meguri's hearts draw closer.
「少しずつ　心の距離を縮めていく
誠司と巡璃」
「やがて　２人は→
And eventually, they confirm their feelings for each other and enter a relationship.
互いの気持ちを確かめ合い
結ばれる」
（恵）わ～　わ～　わぁ～！
おお…　これは！
Wow, even though she's based on Katou,
she really has that heart-pounding feeling!
加藤がモデルのくせに
キュンキュンくるなぁ！
（英梨々）あんたは
ナレーションに専念してなさい！
How about you just stick to the narration?!
「しかし
それと　時期を同じくして→
But that's when Meguri's behavior
starts slowly changing.
巡璃の様子が
少しずつ変わっていく」
Her strange obsession with Seiji...
「誠司への異様な執着」
Her recurring subconscious fear...
「時折見せる　無意識の恐怖心」
「生まれる前の時代の記憶」
Her memories of a time before birth...
「そんな　ある日
様子のおかしい　巡璃を心配して→
One day, Seiji worries about Meguri's erratic behavior and calls out to her,
声を掛けた　誠司に
彼女は　突然　こう呼び掛ける」
when suddenly, she refers
to him in an unexpected way.
はい　加藤！
（恵）えっ？　ああ　えっと…。→
You're up, Katou!
Huh? O-Oh, um...
「ううん。
何でもないよ　お兄ちゃん」
"No, nothing's wrong, Onii-chan."
お兄ちゃん　きたぁ～っ！
（英梨々）やかましい！
She said "Onii-chan"!
Keep it down!
「やがて　前世の自分を…」
At last, Meguri begins
recalling her previous life.
「その道ならぬ恋や
一族の悲劇を思い出していく巡璃」
Her immoral love...
The tragedy in her family...
「彼女が
記憶を取り戻していくたびに→
As she regains more of her memories,
inexplicable events begin to
occur around the two of them.
２人の周囲に
不可解な出来事が起こり始める」
Finally, an enemy appears before them,
whose life goes back through centuries of history.
「そして　とうとう
２人の前に現れる→
数百年もの長い歴史を
生き永らえてきた　最強の敵」
うおぉぉ～！
今度は　超展開だぜ！
Whoa! This is one hell of a plot twist!
（英梨々）ハァ…　もう…。
Ugh... Sheesh...
「とうとう　お互いを守るため
敵と戦うことを決意した→
Eventually, in order to protect each other, the two lovers, once older brother and younger sister, resolve to fight!
かつての兄と妹にして
恋人同士の２人！」
（恵）え～　きょうだいで
恋人同士って　なくない？
Huh? Isn't it a bit inappropriate
for siblings to be in love?
What are you talking about, Katou?
何言ってんだ　加藤！
あるんだよ　２次元には！
It's more than appropriate in the 2D realm!
（英梨々）
そうよ　倫也の言うとおりよ。→
Yes, Tomoya's exactly right.
もう少し　真面目に
やってくれない？　加藤さん。
Can't you take this a bit more seriously, Katou-san?
（恵）えっ？　澤村さん？
Huh? Sawamura-san?
「そして　最終決戦！」
Finally, the final battle!
「激しい戦いの後　ついに勝利して
過去の悲劇の連鎖を断ち切る２人」
The two prevail in the fierce battle, thus ending
the repeating tragedy they'd faced through many lives!
「愛し合う　きょうだいは　とうとう長い時を経て　結ばれる…」
The sibling lovers are finally united at long last!
Go, Katou!
はい　加藤！
（恵）あ～　はいはい　えっと…。→
Okay, okay. Um...
「これからも　ずっと一緒だね。
愛してるよ　お兄ちゃん」
"We'll always be together from now on.
I love you, Onii-chan."
Hnngh!
あ～…！　きたきたきたきた！
再び　お兄ちゃん　きたぁぁ～っ！！
It's so happening!
She called him "Onii-chan" again!
The line itself hits the sweet spot,
but it's hardly worth anything with acting like that.
（英梨々）せりふ　そのものは
ぐっとくるんだけど→
その投げやりな演技は
何とかならない？
（恵）ごめん　私　まだ
２次元の作法ってのになれなくて。
Sorry, I still haven't gotten
used to the ways of 2D.
So, what do you think?
それで　感想は？
うん　面白いよ　これ。
It's really exciting!
今までの　霞　詩子作品とは
全然　方向性が違うけど→
It goes in a completely different direction from your Kasumi Utako works,
but it's so full of tension and plot twists.
盛り上がりも　サプライズも
ふんだんに　ちりばめられてて→
I was lost for breath at
every new development!
息もつかせぬ展開で。
So the main heroine was the protagonist's
younger sister in her past life, as well as a yandere.
（英梨々）メインヒロインが
前世では　妹だとか→
しかも　どう見てもヤンデレだとかあなたらしくない　あざとさよね。
It was uncharacteristically sly of you.
まっ　でも　嫌いじゃないわ。
But well, I didn't find it quite bad.
えっと　設定が　凝ってると思った。
Um... I thought the premise was quite elaborate.
あ～…　そうだな。
（恵）ん？　うん？
Yeah, it was.
Well, still, it doesn't seem
anyone has any objections.
まあ　でも　どうやら
否定的な意見もないようだし→
これが　決定稿ってことで？
えっ？
So should we call this the final draft?
Fine by me.
（英梨々）いいんじゃない？
こっちのキャラデザも→
I need to get character designs finalized soon,
so we'd be better off having the plot ready ASAP.
そろそろ　本格的に
入らないといけないから→
プロットが早いに
越したことないし。
それじゃあ
これで　完成ということで。
Well then, it's finally finished.
ちょっと待って！
Hang on a second!
（詩羽）倫理君？
Mr. Ethical?
It's definitely exciting. I have nothing to complain about in that regard.
確かに　面白い。
文句なく　面白いんだけど…。
But I'd like some time to think
about it before green-lighting it.
でも　もうちょっとだけ
結論を　待ってほしいんだ。
Dating Sim Proposal
Give it a rest, Tomoya.
（英梨々）いいかげんにしなさいよ
倫也！→
It's been three days now!
もう　３日も塩漬けじゃない！
ごめん。
Sorry.
何もしないどころか
足を引っ張るだけ。
Not only aren't you doing anything yourself,
but you're restraining your artists,
destroying their morale!
作り手の　モチベーションを
下げるだけ。
こんなの　典型的な
百害あって一利なしなディレクターよ。
You're the very image of an
"all pain, no gain" type of director.
もういいじゃない。
これで　十分　面白いじゃない。
Isn't this good enough?
It's plenty exciting already.
あんただって
そう言ったじゃない。→
You said so yourself, didn't you?
だから　先に進もうよ。
So let's just move on already.
I'm sorry. I can't allow that.
ごめん　それはできない。
（英梨々）倫也！
Tomoya!
確かに　面白いけど
すごいんだけど→
It's definitely exciting. It's amazing.
何か　これじゃ
満足できないんだよ　俺。
But something about it just doesn't satisfy me.
そんな　感覚的なこと言われても
訳分かんないよ！
Such subjective criticism based on your feelings isn't going to get us anywhere!
Yeah. I wish I could explain what
I mean better. I know that's wrong.
うん。　正しく伝えられないのは
俺が悪い。
But even so, I can't approve of this.
I just can't call it my work in its current state.
それでも　駄目だ。　このままじゃ
俺の作品じゃなくなる。
Then why don't you write it yourself?
だったら
自分で書けばいいじゃない。
（詩羽）それを言ったら
おしまいよ　澤村さん。
If you start saying things like that,
you'll be finished, Sawamura-san.
なっ…！？
（詩羽）ディレクターが　クリエーターに対して→
You know that there are certain things
a director should never say to his creators.
言ってはいけないことが
あるように→
クリエーターが　ディレクターに
言ってはいけないこともあるのよ。
Likewise, there are certain things
creators should never say to their directors.
今のが　それ。
You just said one of them.
霞ヶ丘　詩羽！　あんた…
あたしが　いったい誰のために！
Kasumigaoka Utaha!
Who do you think I'm trying to help here?
少なくとも
今のは　私のためじゃない。
I don't know. But that last thing
you said doesn't help me.
（詩羽）またなんだ…。
えっ？
It's happening again.
また　答えをくれないのね　倫理君。
You won't give me an answer
this time either, Mr. Ethical.
（恵）安芸君。→
Aki-kun...
あのさ　あしたの
約束のことなんだけどさ。
Um, about our promise to go
to Rokutenba Mall tomorrow...
六天馬モールに出掛けるって話。
Oh. The weekend's already here?
そっか　もう週末か。
あれ　延期しよう。　ねっ？
加藤…。
Let's postpone that, shall we?
Katou...
今は　そんな気分じゃないよね。
だから　また今度。　ねっ？
You're not really in the
right mood for it now, aren't you?
So let's go some other time.
安芸君？
Aki-kun?
No, let's still go.
いや　やっぱ　行こう。
えっ？
We'll go on that date tomorrow.
あした　デートしよう。
≪（物音）
（恵）ん？
デート　してみよう　俺たち。
We'll try this date thing, then?
There are so many people here!
（恵）すっごい人だね～。
お…　おう。
Y-Yeah.
But it's still fun.
でも　楽しみだな～。
何軒くらい　回れるかな？
I wonder how many times it wraps around.
大丈夫？　安芸君。
へ…　平気。
Are you all right, Aki-kun?
I-I'm fine.
Do you feel okay? Does the crowd put you off?
気分　悪いの？
もしかして　人混みに酔った？
違う。　人混みは　平気なんだ。
No, I'm fine with crowds.
それが　統率された
オタクの集団だったらな。
Crowds of otaku under
some sort of leadership, anyway.
それは　私が苦手かもしれない。
I think I would be less than fine with that.
Katou, does this really not bother you at all?
加藤　お前は
本当に気にならないのか？
この無秩序なリア充の群れが。
This chaotic throng of normals.
Uh, whether they're normals aside,
this is typical of a sale, isn't it?
えっと　リア充はともかく
バーゲンって　こんなもんでしょ？
Is it?
そうなの？
≪（ざわめき）
あっ　開いたよ　安芸君。
Ah, it's open, Aki-kun!
Sorry to call for a break after waiting in line all morning and everything.
ごめん。
せっかく　朝一で並んだのに→
いきなり休憩とか…。
ううん。　こっちこそ　ごめんね。
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
何で　こんなに
行列になれてないんだよ　みんな。
How can these people be so bad at forming lines?
統率もとれず
右往左往するだけのスタッフ。
The staff just look back and forth
without even trying to manage the chaos.
The customers just barge in
and break lines all over the place.
平気で　割り込み　列を乱す客。
しかも　このカップル率の高さ！
And there are couples as far as the eye can see!
滅びろ　リア充ども！
Just die, normals!
Well, our intentions aside,
we appear to be contributing to that.
まあ　私たちも　実情は　ともかく→
はたから見れば
その比率　上げてるんだけど。
これが
アウェーの洗礼ってやつか…。
So this is my away game baptism.
やってくれるぜ　六天馬モール。
You're a tough opponent, Rokutenba Mall.
言ってることは
全然　分からないけど→
I have no idea what you're saying,
せめて　オープンして
ひと月くらい　たってから→
but I guess we should've waited at least
a month after it opened before coming.
来るべきだったね。
No, I think coming anytime
would've been the same.
いや　たぶん　いつ来ても同じだ。
そうなのかな？
You think so?
だって　これは
人数の問題じゃない。
I mean, the issue isn't the numbers.
It's the mindset of the people participating.
参加者の意識の問題だ。
（恵）意識？
Their mindset?
俺の知る　日本一の大行列は
こんなもんじゃない。
The longest queue in Japan
I know is nothing like this.
誰も通路を走ったり
エスカレーターを歩いたり→
No one runs down the aisles,
walks on the escalators, or cuts into the line.
列に割り込んだりしない。
誰もが　参加者だという意識を
高く持ち→
People are highly aware
that they're actual participants
自分たちのイベントを
成功させようという→
and brim with enthusiasm
for making their event a success.
熱意であふれている。
Ah, you're talking about Comic Thingy, right?
あ～　確か　コミック何ちゃら
ってやつだっけ？
It's not "Comic Thingy"!
何ちゃらじゃない！
コミックマーケットだ！　コミックマーケット！
It's called Comic Market!
通称　コミケ。
夏と冬の　年２回　開催。
Also known as Comiket!
It runs twice a year, in summer and winter.
More than 500,000 people gather for
the largest doujinshi sales event in Japan—
３日間の開催期間中に
５０万人以上　集める　日本一…。
いやいやいや！
世界一の同人誌　販売イベントを→
No, in the world! And you call
something so grand "Comic Thingy"?!
そんな　適当な略称で
呼ぶんじゃない！
Wow, you sure livened up all of a sudden.
あっ　何か　急に元気になった。
そう　コミケだったら　俺は→
Yes, at Comiket I would never
show such an unsightly appearance!
こんな　ぶざまな姿を
さらしたりしない！
たとえ　今の１０倍以上の人数が
押し寄せてきたとしても…！
Not even if ten times this many people were crowded in here.
Oh, of course! That was the problem.
Well, we're not at Comiket,
so there's not much we can do.
そうか…　そうだったのか。
（恵）まあ　コミケとかいう→
やつじゃないし　しょうがないよ。
いや　しょうがなくなんかない。
No, there is something we can do.
I just have to think of them as otaku.
オタクだと思うんだ。
These guys are my people.
My lovable asswipes of people.
ここにいるのは　俺たちだ。
愛すべき　クソ野郎どもだ。
Aki-kun?
安芸君？
加藤→
Katou, list all the stores you wanted to visit today.
今日　お前が行きたかった店を
全部　教えてくれ。
このフロアマップに
チェックを入れるだけでいい。
You can just mark them on the map.
Huh? But if I listed all of them,
do you know how many there'd be?
えっ？　けど　全部だと　かなり
たくさんの　お店になっちゃうよ。
Don't worry about it.
いいよ。
とにかく　まずは全部だ。
For now, just put them all down.
動線は…　うん　こっちだな。
So the conducting line...
Yeah, that's it.
となると　順路を　こう結んで
南から北への流れは　こうで。
Which means if we connect the route here,
then our path from south to north would go like...
加藤。
ん？
Katou.
Hm?
この２つのサークル…
じゃなくて→
Which one of these two circles—
I mean, stores—should be more popular?
２つの店って　どっちが人気ある？
ん～と　そうだな…。
やっぱり　手前の方じゃないかな。
Hm, let me think...
Probably the one closer to the entrance.
なら　少し遠くなるが　左回りが…。
Then counter-clockwise would
be better, albeit a little long,
俺のせいで出遅れてるからな。
ここは　慎重に…。
since we're starting late because of me.
Need to be careful here.
別に　そんなに悩まなくても→
You really don't need to worry about it so much.
適当に回って
入れるお店に入ればいいよ。
We can just go around however
and visit the stores that we can.
I won't allow this to become a war of attrition beyond what I've marked off!
俺が仕切る以上
無駄な消耗戦にはさせない！
安芸君？
さあ　加藤→
Aki-kun?
Now then, Katou...
アウェーでも勝ちに行くぞ。
逆転だ！
I'm gonna win this away game.
It's time to turn the tables!
お待たせ～。
ああ。　お目当ての物は　買えたか？
Sorry for the wait!
Hey, did you get to buy what you came for?
ばっちり。
よし　次だ。　このまま　北へ流れる。
Got it exactly!
Great. On to the next one.
We'll make our way north from here.
あれ？　もう一軒　回る所
なかったっけ？
Wait, doesn't that skip
another place we were going to?
情報によると　残念ながら
そっちは　２時間待ちらしい。
It's unfortunate, but info sources
show that the wait there is about two hours.
Whoa. I guess we're giving up on that one, then.
うわ　じゃあ　もう
諦めるしかないね。
No, it's too soon to say yet.
いや　その判断は　まだ早い。
どうやら　今は
今日の限定品　目当ての客で→
By the looks of things, at the moment it's crammed with people who're after today-only items.
ごった返しているらしい。
Once those are sold out, it should clear up.
だが　それが完売したら
一気にすくはず。
状況は　目まぐるしく変わるから
綿密な情報収集と→
The situation is changing rapidly,
so our ability to gather precise information and
some flexibility in our plan are going to be key!
フレキシブルな判断が
重要になってくるぞ。
うわ～　ただの買い物に
そこまでやるんだ。
I can't believe how seriously you're taking a simple shopping trip.
Otaku and normals both understand the pain of being
unable to buy something they looked forward to, don't they?
楽しみにしてた品物を
買えなかったときの→
悔しさや　悲しさは　オタクでも
リア充でも　変わらないだろ？
まっ　そうかもね。
Well, I guess they must.
Let's go, Katou!
行くぞ　加藤！　高度な情報戦は
すでに始まっている！
This high-stakes information
warfare has already begun!
了解。
Roger!
頑張れ。　あと　もうちょいだ。
Keep it up.
We're almost finished.
何か　お昼過ぎたら
また　人　増えてきたね。
It seems like even more people
are here now that it's afternoon.
この連絡通路さえクリアすれば
余裕ができる。
If we can just clear this overpass,
we'll have a surplus of time.
頑張れ。
（恵）う…　うん。
Don't give up yet.
O-Okay.
キャッ！
Katou!
加藤！
あっ…。
行くぞ。　離すなよ。
We're moving. Don't let go.
Aki-kun...
安芸君。
ぬお～！　うう…！　うう…！
We made it!
着いた～　ここが　最後のお店だよ。
This is the last store!
いよっしゃ～！　イェーイ！
Hell yeah!
ホント　まさか　一日で
回れるとは思ってなかったよ。
Honestly, I never thought we'd be able to get everything done in one day.
お疲れさま　安芸君。
You must be tired, Aki-kun.
I don't want to hear that.
お疲れさまって言うな…。
You reminded me of how tired I really am.
疲れてたの思い出すだろ。
アハハ　しばらく
そこで　休んでていいよ。
You can just rest here for a little while.
I'll take you up on that.
そうさせてもらう。
フフッ。
あれ？　おい　この店って…。
Huh? Hey, this store's...
うん　いい感じ。
似合ってるよ。
Yeah, not bad. These suit you.
えっと　たぶん。
Um, I think.
加藤？
今日　付き合ってくれた　お礼。
Katou?
These are for coming with me today.
ありがとね　安芸君。
Thanks, Aki-kun.
加藤。
ん？
Katou...
Hm?
Oh, just...
いや　その…。
ありがとう。
Thanks.
Not at all.
どういたしまして。
But... I'm sorry. I won't be able to see you home.
けれど　ごめん。
帰り　送れなくなった。
今すぐ　行かなくちゃならない所があるんだ。
There's somewhere I need to go right away.
bye-bye no ato samenai binetsu
After every good-bye, my cheeks are always warm
w
yokaze ni fukare kangaeru
And as I feel the wind against them, I always think
suki kirai kirai suki kurikaesu
Love? Hate? Hate? Love? Over and over
sono hitomi ni utsutteiru no wa
What are you seeing in those eyes of yours?
real sore tomo nijigen
Reality or something 2-D?
tayasuku kawaii da nante iwanai de yo ne
Don't just say I look pretty like it's no big deal to me
ashita mo me wo kosutte ohayou wo itte
Tomorrow, you'll rub your eyes and say "good morning"
tawai mo nai koto takusan oshiete
And talk about all sorts of pointless stuff
sukoshizutsu chikadzuiteku kyori ni
And as we slowly grow closer together
doushiyou jibun ja nai mitai da
What do I do? What am I usually like?
merry-go-round ga tomaranakute
This merry-go-round just never stops
mawaru mawaru keshiki ga kawatteku
Spinning, spinning, the scenery blurs by
colorful na yume wo miru
Like a colorful dream
dokudoku shite karadajuu wo
Throb, throb, I can feel them inside
meguru meguru kimochi
Going 'round and 'round, these feelings
mada kotoba ni dekinakute
I still can't put them into words
hitokoto sore de juubun nanoni
Even though one word would be enough